askfrank.net 2011-12-24

# Privacy Policy Provided by SEO Services in Destin Florida-Search Engine Optimization Company

**OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

www.AskFrank.net is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time.

In addition, online visitors who wish to purchase a membership through our Web site must provide their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card number and expiration date. All credit card transactions occur over a secure connection.

All online visitor data collected by www.AskFrank.net is protected against unauthorized access. We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations.

Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. www.AskFrank.net encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child’s online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child’s information is treated.

Check out the FTC’s site  <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec08.shtm>  for more tips on protecting children’s privacy online.

Contacting Us.

We can be reached by contacting:

981 Hwy 98E Ste 3,  
Destin, FL32541  
850.659.3027 Office  
850.460.6506  Cell  
877.841.4024  Fax  
www.AskFrank.net  
Email: admin[at]askfrank.net 

This entry was posted on Friday, September 21st, 2001 at 3:54 pm and is filed under [Destin SEO](http://www.askfrank.net/advertising/will-ask-you-to/ "View all posts in Destin SEO"). You can follow any responses to this entry through the [RSS 2.0](http://www.askfrank.net/privacy_policy/feed/) feed. Responses are currently closed, but you can [trackback](http://www.askfrank.net/privacy_policy/trackback/) from your own site.
